Guide to the Historic Photograph Subject File circa 19th century-20th century
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 11: Indians
  - Chief Garry's pipe and hymnal and Chief Joseph's record sticks, 2 items (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Blackfoot child in papoose, 1 item (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Color postcards of Blackfoot Indians, 5 items (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "Petroglyph" on Buck Mountain, 1 item (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Petroglyphs at Buffalo Eddy, Snake River, 9 items (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Petroglyphs at Rock Island, Columbia River, 7 items (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Various petroglyph and pictograph sites, 9 items (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Archaeological excavation by Dr. Richard Daugherty, 1 item (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Stick game- Nespelem women, 1 item (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Makah at Neah Bay- community potlatch, 1 item (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Fort Hall, ID- dancing in ceremony c. 1897, 2 items (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Nespelem dances, 5 items (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - War dances at Coupeville, Toppenish, Bannock, 3 items (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Cabins at St. Mary's Mission, Nespelem, and Lowden, 4 items (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Nez Perce Agency, 2 items (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Statue dedication, 2 items (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Euro-American misc. photos from Fort Hall and Teton Pass, 5 items (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Old Chief Joseph Burial, Oregon, 1 item (Box 18, Folder 23.1)
- Series 12: Lakes and Rivers
  - Lake Okanogan and Lake Omak, B.C., 2 items (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Gold Creek- Longview, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Coeur D'Alene Lake, ID, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 2.1)
  - Priest Lake, ID, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 2.2)
  - Post Falls, ID, 2 items (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Salmon River, ID, 2 items (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Snake River, ID, 24 items (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - St. Joe River, ID, 5 items (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lake Cocolalla, ID, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Hayden Lake, ID, 3 items (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Priest Lake and Lake Coeur D'Alene, ID, 4 items (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Crater Lake, OR, 20 items (Box 19, Folder 9.1)
  - Deschutes River, OR, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 9.2)
  - Glacier Lake, OR, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 9.3)
  - Hood River, OR, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Hood Canal, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 10.1)
  - Powder and Wallowa Rivers, OR, 2 items (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Wahkeena Falls, OR, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Lake Chelan, WA, 18 items (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Lake Cle Elum and Fish Lake, WA, 5 items (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Conconully Reservoir, WA, 1933, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Lake Crescent, WA, inc. falls 1894, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Lake Crescent, WA, 10 items (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Diablo Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Dry Falls and Grand Coulee, WA, 14 items (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Echo Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Findley Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Fortune Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Lake Keechelus, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Park Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 23.1)
  - Picture Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Steilacoom Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Surprise Lake, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Twin Lakes, WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Jackson Lake, WY, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 27.1)
  - Lake Quinault, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Lake Wenatchee, 3 items (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Mountain Lake on Orcas Island, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Lakes in Spokane Region, 3 items (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Cedar R., WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Chelan R., WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Upper Cispus R., WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Colville R., WA, 2 items (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Deep Creek Canyon, WA, 5 items (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Elwha R., WA, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Great Falls, MT, 3 items (Box 19, Folder 37.1)
  - Horsetail Falls, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Lower Bonnington Falls, Nelson, BC, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 38.5)
  - Metaline Falls, Box Canyon, 7 items (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Palouse Falls, 5 items (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Palouse River, 4 items (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Pend Oreille R., 2 items (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Rex River, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Sauk River, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Skagit River, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Snoqualmie Falls, 2 items (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Soleduck [Sol Duc] River, 1 item (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Spokane River, 23 items (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Spokane River, 11 item (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rainbow Falls (Stehekin River), 2 items (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Little White Salmon Falls, 1 item (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Wind River Falls, 1 item (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Wind River Falls, 1 item (Box 20, Folder 4.1)
  - Yakima River, 2 items (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Douglass Lake, 1 item (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Logjam on a river c. 1936, 1 item (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Old water mill, 1 item (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mountain lake, 1 item (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Various lakes and rivers, 17 items (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Series 13: Logging
  - Near Stanwood, WA, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Logging roads, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Spruce and Cedar Trees, 3 items (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Undercutting Douglass Fir, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Preparing to burn a stump, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Clearing stumps, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Big Creek area, ID, after fire of 1910., 8 items (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Big Creek salvage logging view, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Big Creek salvage logging- donkey engine and crew 2, items (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - General logging photos, 7 items (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Logging scene, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Logging scene c. 1950, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Tree topping, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Stacking timber near Priest R., ID c. 1920, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Lumberyard with horses, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Four principle timber varieties in the NW, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Cedars in Ohanapecosh Valley, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Potlatch Co. lands- "White Pine and Elk River Dist.", 5 items (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Forest scenes, 12 items (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Forest after fires, 3 items (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Cedar River Trail, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Forest along Pacific Hwy., 1 item (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Potlatch and Palouse R. Dams, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - A fallen monarch, OR, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Potlatch Co.- White Pine logs, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Douglass Fir, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Big logs and stumps, 4 items (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Cedar Stump- Sedro-Wooley, WA c. 1907, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Fir Trees and reforested land, 4 items (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Wind River Forest nursery, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Bellingham Nursery, Whatcom Co., WA, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Reforestation project at Walsh Lake, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Potlatch Lumber Co. barns and houses, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Potlatch Co.- general managers and houses, 3 items (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Potlatch Co.- president Charles A. Weyerhaeuser, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Potlatch Co.- officials' homes, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - The town of Potlatch, ID- business district, 4 items (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Potlatch- homes, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Potlatch- barns, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - The town of Potlatch, ID- school, church, etc., 5 items (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Potlatch- passenger train, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - St. Maries, ID, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - A day in the life of a forester, 5 items (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Houses along St. Joe River c. 1900 and 1908, 7 items (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Potlatch Co.- forester, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Blackie Joe's cabin, St. Joe R. country, 1900, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Forest Camp cookhouse, c. 1900, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Pioneer Forest Ranger, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Potlatch logging camp, 4 items (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Timber Cruiser's camp, 1 item (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Logging camp scenes c. 1936, 3 items (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Bob White's logging camp- St. Joe City, ID 1908, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Early camp (1900) in St. Joe R. country, 2 items (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Potlatch Co.- sawmill and power plant, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Longview, WA- lumber mill, 3 items (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Ostrander mill, Cowlitz Co., 1 item (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oppenheimer mill, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Longview mill, 3 items (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Colony lumber mill, 1887, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Almota, WA mill (note: flour mill, not lumber), 1 item (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Two-man power sawmill, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Warehouse and sawmill- Elberton, WA 1888, 2 items (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Sawmill scenes, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Portable "gyppo" sawmill, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Portland sawmill, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Ione, WA sawmill, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Milwaukee Lumber Co, St Joe, ID 1908, 2 items (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sawmill scenes, 2 items (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Potlatch Co., planing mill, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Potlatch Co., sawmill, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Potlatch Co., "preparing the way", 1 item (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Everett, WA- Weyerhaeuser mill, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Hoquiam- Spruce veneer plant, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - NW Lumber Co. - Hoquiam, WA, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Lumber yards, 5 items (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Potlatch- lumber yards and shed, 6 items (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Export lumber- Port of Seattle, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Pulpwood Loading- Quillayute, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Loading logs- Grays Harbor, 2 items (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Spruce from Neah Bay, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Logs on river w. sailing ships, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Logging with horses, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Potlatch Co.- hauling logs w. horses, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Steam powered "CAT", 1 item (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Clearing land with Caterpillars, 10 items (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Sawfiler, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Steam donkeys, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Logs awaiting steam donkey, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Diesel powered equipment, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Rand stump burner c. 1910, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Potlatch Co.- log storage ponds, 3 items (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Potlatch Co.- trains hauling logs, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Tracks into logging area, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Logging trains- post cards, 2 items (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Potlatch Co.- associated railways, 10 items (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Potlatch Co.- Railways at Potlatch, ID, 4 items (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Logging truck, 2 items (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Potlatch Co.- water works pumping station, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Potlatch Co.- roundhouse, machine and car repair, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Potlatch Co.- locomotive equipment, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Ocean freighter carrying lumber for export, 1 item (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Hepfinger's Western Washington Exhibit, large spruce felled in Aberdeen, 6 items (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Series 14: Mining
  - Inspiration Copper Co., AZ, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Coeur d'Alene mining districts, 15 items (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bunker Hill Mine, ID, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Mining scenes, ID, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Zinc plant, Kellogg, ID, 1928, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Tiger Mine, Burks, ID, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Hoosier Quarry, Indiana, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Sand Dredge, Virginia City, MT, 1935, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mine Butte, MT: Anaconda, Pennsylvania, Minnie Healy, Washoe smelter, 6 items (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Mining scenes, MT, 4 items (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Roslyn, WA- mine explosion, 1909, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Treasure State mining, Blewett Mts, MT, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Mine near Republic, WA, 7 items (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Coal Mine, Bellingham, WA, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Miners, WA, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Placer mine prospect tunnels, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Mine scenes, Cascade Mts, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - B and H Mill after explosion, 1899, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Continental Coal Co., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Mining scenes- miners, 4 items (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Mining scenes- structures, 4 items (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Quarries, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Nugget found in Murray, ID, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 22.1)
- Series 15: Mercantile Stores
  - Confectionary, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - M.A. Rose Jewelry Store, Colfax, WA, c. 1900, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Saloon, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Hillyard Pharmacy, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Mercantile Buildings, 8 items (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - General Stores, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - General Stores, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Series 16: Monuments
  - Gravestone of Princess Angelina, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Arlington, WA- historical tree, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Astoria Monument, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Canip, WA, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Replica of first Capitol Building, WA Territory, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Old Cataldo Mission- drawing, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Cataldo Mission, Cataldo, ID, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 35.1)
  - Soldier's monument, Colfax, WA, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Col. Isaac N. Ebey memorial, Coupeville, WA, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Monument to soldiers killed at Custer's Last Stand, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Doughboy statue, Seattle, WA, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Jefferson Peace and Friendship Medal- distributed by Lewis and Clark, 4 items (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - General Lafayette memorial, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Stonehenge monument, Maryhill, WA, 3 items (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Maryhill Castle and Museum, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Stevens Indian Treaty tablet, Mukilteo, WA, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Sharp's 50 caliber buffalo gun, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Mullan Rd., 1 item (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Nisqually plaque, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Oregon Trail monument, Expedition, 1906, 4 items (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Spaulding monument, Lapwai, ID, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Treaty Gun tree, Chehalis, WA, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Tshimikain Mission, Walker's Prairie, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - First Colony on Puget Sound, Oct. 1845, Tumwater, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Pioneer Cemetery, Union Gap, WA, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Beach near Capt. Vancouver's landing site, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - George Washington statue, 2 items (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Whitman grave and monument, 4 items (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Marcus Whitman statue, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Basalt stone monument, Wishram, 1 item (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - "The Wreckage", 2 items (Box 23, Folder 59)
- Series 17: Mountains
  - Main divide near Lakeview, ID, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Thompson's Bluffs, Clark Fork R. (moved to PC 22), 0 items (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Mt. Missoula, Clark's Fork R (moved to PC 22), 0 items (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Mt. Adams, 3 items (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Mt. Adams, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Mt. Baker, 4 items (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mt. Baker Hwy., 4 items (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Mt. Baker, 6 items (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Mt. Baker, 5 items (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Mt. Baker and Chain Lake, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Baldy Mountain near Morton, WA, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Mt. Constance, Olympic Mts, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Mt. Constitution, Orcas Island, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mt. Olympus, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Mt. Rainier, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Skiing on Mt. Rainier, 4 items (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Mt. Rainier Park, 4 items (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Mt. Rainier Crater, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Climbers on Mt. Rainier, 4 items (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Mt. Rainier park scenes, 11 items (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Mt. Rainier Paradise Inn, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Mt. Rainier, Sunrise Park, 3 items (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Mt. Rainier, 18 items (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Mt. Seattle, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Mt. Shuksan, 4 items (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Mt. Shuksan, 5 items (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Mt. Spokane, 5 items (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Mt. St. Helens eruption aftermath, 3 itemw (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Cascade Mts., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Skykomish River and Cascade Mountains, WA, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 30.1)
  - Cascades- Skagit R., Ruby Basin, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Mt. Index, WA, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 31.1)
  - Cascade Mountains, 6 items (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Glacier National Park, 67 items (Box 24, Folder 32.1)
  - Famous Mountains of Washington, 13 items (Box 24, Folder 32.2)
  - Olympic Mts., 2 items (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Olympic Mts.- Camp Marion, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Olympic Mts., 7 items (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Olympic Mts.- horse packing, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Cedar R. Valley, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Tatoosh Range, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Huckleberry Mts., 1 item (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Snoqualmie Pass, 4 items (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Stevens Pass, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Rim Rock Plateau and Chelan Lake, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Chelan Nat'l Forest, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Leavenworth, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Cabin near Newport, WA, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Paricutin volcano, 1943, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Unidentified and Mt. Rainier, 11 item (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Misc. Mountain Climbing and Skiing, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Jasper Park, Canada, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 48.1)
  - White Pass, Canada, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 48.2)
  - Unidentified mountain scenes, 3 items (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Pilot Butte Canal, Crook County, OR, 2 items (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Central Oregon Canal, Crook County, OR, 1 item (Box 24, Folder 51)
- Series 18: Pacific Northwest
  - Relief map of Washington, 3 items (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Sagebrush, eastern WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Steptoe Butte, 4 items (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Kamiak Butte, views from, 7 items (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Palouse County, 2 items (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Farmland near Spokane, 2 items (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Goldendale grade, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Gingko petrified forest, 3 items (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Dry Falls, WA, 7 items (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Deep Creek Canyon, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln Rock, Entiat, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Tenino Mounds, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Surveying Washington State c. 1890, 13 items (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 13.1)
  - Olympic Loop Hwy, near Discovery Bay, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lummi Island from Chuckanut Drive, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - San Juan Islands, 5 items (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Beach at Larush, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Surf Cave on Washington Sea Coast (postcard - Asahel Curtis), 1 item (Box 25, Folder 17.5)
  - Building a forest trail, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Long Beach, WA- aerial view, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Cake Rock, Callahan Co., WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Columbia Basin project- recreational, 5 items (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Columbia Basin Project- agricultural, 15 items (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Columbia Basin project- coulees and canals, 7 items (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Prehistoric Rock carving- petroglyph, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Stage Coach barns in Spokane and Stevens Cos., 2 items (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - St. Joseph's Mission- Antrim, Yakima Co., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Washington pioneer homes, 9 items (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Washington pioneer homes, 13 items (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - U.S. Forest officer's camp- Colville Nat'l Forest, 1913, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Cabin near Puget Sound, 1907, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Elliot Bay, Seattle, WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 30.1)
  - Puget Sound region - Album of panoramic photos from Carl Morrow, ca. 1911, 12 items (Box 25, Folder 30.5)
  - Lighthouses in Washington State, 9 items (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - The Lighthouse Inn, La Conner, Washington, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 31.1)
  - Modern light tower- Burnis Pt., Tacoma, 2 items (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Seattle City Lights Botanical Garden, 4 items (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Old school house- built in 1879, Lincoln Co., 1 item (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Capital Building- WA territory, 3 items (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Courthouse- WA territory, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Conconully, WA, 2 items (Box 25, Folder 36.1)
  - Old Molson, WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 36.2)
  - Okanogan Valley, 1934, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Okanogan Valley, B.C., 4 items (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Cattle in Okanogan Forest, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Canadian Rockies near Banff, Alberta, 10 items (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Lewis and Clark Trail, ID and MT, 4 items (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Armitage, MT- aerial view, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Chinese oven along railroad track (on Snake R.?), 1 item (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Various Oregon Images, 36 items (Box 25, Folder 43.1)
  - Southern Oregon, 4 items (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Oregon Coast, 4 items (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - North Schuyenni Canyon, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Black Canyon, 3 items (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Cheyenne Canyon, 5 items (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Naches Pass Wagon Road, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Fontenae Convent, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Miner's Ridge, Cascade Mts, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Coastline, Sept 1922, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Clallum Bay, WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 52.1)
  - Sacajawea State Park, WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 52.2)
  - Outdoor life, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Cannon Beach, OR, 2 items (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Coral Gardens, OR, 3 items (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Petersen's Rock Garden, OR, 23 items (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Salt Cairn - OR, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Cape Foulweather/The Lookout, 3 items (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Ginkgo Petrified Forest State Park, WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Chuckanut Gardens, WA, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Frank Slide, Alberta, Canada, 1 item (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Series 19: Pacific Northwest Children
  - Children forming letter "P", 1 item (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Children in park, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lance Hills school children, June 5th, 1903, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Jim Gale school house, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Shrine Auditorium teachers banquet, 1937, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Girls- portraits, 4 items (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Girls- portraits, 6 items (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Girl- casual, 3 items (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Boy- portraits, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Boys- portrait, 7 items (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Boys and girls- portraits, 3 items (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Baby- portrait, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Babies- portrait, 2 items (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Babies- portraits, 11 item (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Baby- portrait, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Mrs. Strauahaus et al, 1902, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Women in Elgin, OR, 3 items (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Women- portraits, 4 items (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Mrs. Prinstead, Elizabeth Skinner, et. al., 4 items (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Women- cabinet cards, 9 items (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Women- cabinet cards, 10 items (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Women- portraits, 3 items (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Women- portraits and miscellaneous sheets, 11 item (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - June Pomeroy (1906) and other portraits, 4 items (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Women and Men- portraits, 1 item (Box 26, Folder 25)